{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "21st Century Literature",
    "Term": "First Quarter",
    "Title": "Literary Elements and Characters in PROMDI@MANILA",
    "LastModified": "15 August 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "W4-PROMDIMANILA.pptx.pdf"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is the composition of a person or any form in a work of fiction?",
      "answer": "Character",
      "choices": [
        "Dynamic/Round Character",
        "Flat Character",
        "Foil Character",
        "Character"
      ],
      "reference": "W4-PROMDIMANILA.pptx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Characters"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of character usually dynamically changes or transforms by the end of the story?",
      "answer": "Dynamic/Round Character",
      "choices": [
        "Flat Character",
        "Dynamic/Round Character",
        "Foil Character",
        "Static Character"
      ],
      "reference": "W4-PROMDIMANILA.pptx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Characters"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of character stays the same at the end of the story and is considered static?",
      "answer": "Flat Character",
      "choices": [
        "Dynamic/Round Character",
        "Flat Character",
        "Foil Character",
        "Round Character"
      ],
      "reference": "W4-PROMDIMANILA.pptx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Characters"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of character stands in contrast to another character, usually emphasizing a particular attribute of a more prominently characterized figure?",
      "answer": "Foil Character",
      "choices": [
        "Flat Character",
        "Dynamic/Round Character",
        "Foil Character",
        "Main Character"
      ],
      "reference": "W4-PROMDIMANILA.pptx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Characters"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is a Filipino poet, novelist, translator and literary scholar in Kinaray-a, Hiligaynon and Filipino?",
      "answer": "Genevieve L. Asenjo",
      "choices": [
        "Marcus Garvey",
        "Juan C. Laya",
        "Carlos Palanca",
        "Genevieve L. Asenjo"
      ],
      "reference": "W4-PROMDIMANILA.pptx.pdf",
      "term": "Author's Background"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose first novel, Lumbay ng Dila, received a citation for the Juan C. Laya Prize for Excellence in Fiction in a Philippine Language?",
      "answer": "Genevieve L. Asenjo",
      "choices": [
        "Genevieve L. Asenjo",
        "Marcus Garvey",
        "Carlos Palanca",
        "Juan C. Laya"
      ],
      "reference": "W4-PROMDIMANILA.pptx.pdf",
      "term": "Author's Background"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the author of \"PROMDI@MANILA\"?",
      "answer": "Genevieve L. Asenjo",
      "choices": [
        "Marcus Garvey",
        "Genevieve L. Asenjo",
        "Juan C. Laya",
        "Carlos Palanca"
      ],
      "reference": "W4-PROMDIMANILA.pptx.pdf",
      "term": "Author's Background"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was named for the large black ants found on the island called \"hantik-hantik\"?",
      "answer": "Hantik",
      "choices": [
        "Antique",
        "Aklan",
        "Hantik",
        "Capiz"
      ],
      "reference": "W4-PROMDIMANILA.pptx.pdf",
      "term": "Setting Background"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the capital of Antique?",
      "answer": "San Jose De Buenavista",
      "choices": [
        "Pandan Bay",
        "Belison",
        "Iloilo",
        "San Jose De Buenavista"
      ],
      "reference": "W4-PROMDIMANILA.pptx.pdf",
      "term": "Setting Background"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the language of Antique?",
      "answer": "Kinaray-A",
      "choices": [
        "Hiligaynon",
        "Filipino",
        "Kinaray-A",
        "Hamtic"
      ],
      "reference": "W4-PROMDIMANILA.pptx.pdf",
      "term": "Setting Background"
    }
  ]
}